trackingmore.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - TrackingMore

  * Trackingmore ("We", "Us" or "Our") take your privacy seriously. We know that data protection is a matter of trust and your privacy is important to us, so we will manage your personal information collected through the websites located at www.trackingmore.com, the mobile applications, the API related services based on our belief of respect for the individual and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By using any of services provided by this website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site.

  * ### 1\. Information We Collect and Use

  * We collect personal information (such as user name / or company name, email address, shipping and credit card information) to grant you access to our Website or to assist us in providing support or services to you. Those information might be collected when you interact with us through the website, such as when you create an account on the website, make an online purchase from us, request customer service or contact us, submit a review or post any user content (as defined in the Terms of Use) on the website; or otherwise submit personal information to Trackingmore.

  * We may also collect technical information (such as your IP address, the address of a referring website or application, the type of web browser or mobile device you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider and the path you take through the Website) to allow the website to work correctly, to allow us to provide our services, to evaluate use of the website, for marketing purposes and to personalize and enhance your interaction with Trackingmore and etc.

  * ### 2\. Cookies

  * Cookies are small data files stored on the hard disk of the users’ computer. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. By using this website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your computer and to our access to cookies in accordance with the terms herein. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our website.

  * ### 3\. Security of Personal Data

  * We are committed to protecting the security of your personal data. Trackingmore will maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When we transmit highly confidential data (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption.

  * However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is one hundred percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

  * ### 4\. Children's Privacy

  * Trackingmore does not intend that any portion of the website will be accessed or used by children under the age of eighteen, and such use is prohibited. The website is designed and intended for adults. By using Trackingmore, you represent that you are at least eighteen years old and understand that you must be at least eighteen years old in order to create an account on the website. We will promptly delete information connected to any account with a registered user who is not at least eighteen years old.

  * ### 5\. Business Transfers and Affiliates

  * In the event that we are involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. This Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. We may also disclose information about you to our corporate affiliates in order to help provide, understand, and improve our services and our affiliates’ services, including the delivery of ads.

  * ### 6\. Ads

  * We work with third-party websites, advertisers, and Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, including Google (collectively, "Ad Companies"). These Ad Companies may send (or "serve") advertisements directly to your browser, from our website, our Toolbar Service, and from other websites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. The information practices of these Ad Companies are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

  * ### 7\. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

  * In no event shall Trackingmore be liable for any consequential damages, even if we knew or should have known of the possibility thereof. These limitations shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by law. in some jurisdictions, some of the foregoing limitations may not apply.

  * ### 8\. External Links

  * The website may provide links to other third party web sites. Even if the third party is affiliated with us through a business partnership or otherwise, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and you access them at your own risk.

  * ### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Trackingmore shall regularly review the sufficiency of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify and change the Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be published on the Platform.

  * ### 10\. Contact Us

  * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at service@trackingmore.org.

  * **Effective:** November 1st, 2016
